Guide to the Citizen Soldier records, 1966-2007
Citizen Soldier records, 1966-2007
- Series IV. Organization/Date: Citizen Soldier, 1966-2007
  - AIDS Testing
    - AIDS and people of color: the discriminatory impact (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Brisbois, John and Ft. Hood: HIV-III Aids-Testing (Box 21, Folder 10-11)
  - Other Health-Related Issues
    - Green, Orlando (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Palmer, (Mike) Charles (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Daniels, Doris (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights/Blacks in Military
    - Civil rights - promotion case - Harris, Harold (1) (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Harris, Harold (2) (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Freeman, Ralph (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Gays in Military
    - Project Lambda (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Nesbitt, Ellen C. (Box 20, Folder 15-19)
    - Clinton's Gay-Ban, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 12-14)
    - Grimes, Phillip E., 1985-1988 (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
    - Gay rights: military, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 17-18)
    - Caraway, John, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Nesbitt, Ellen C., 1983-1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Military Justice
    - Leavenworth, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Newak, Joanne (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Howard, Joseph (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Yolanda Huet-Vaughn, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
    - D. K. Jefferson, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Bryan, Roberto Enrique (murder case in Panama) (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Cassatt, Allen (gun smuggling case in Grenada) (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Duncan, Dale, Lt. Col. (covert operations) (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - U.S.S. Iowa (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Recruiting Practices
    - Higgins, Craig S. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Crump, Cresta (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Riquelme, John (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Ruiz, Frank (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Conscientious Objectors
    - Bailey, Bob (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Cobos, Daniel (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Huey-Vaughn, Yolanda (Box 27, Folder 39-40)
    - Moctezuma, Steve, Tricia, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Vietnam Veterans
    - Wayne Felde Defense Work, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Michaud, Tom (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Jacko, Ron (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Persian Gulf
    - Military registers, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Zamin, (John) Rudolf, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Atkinson, Stephanie, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Musslewhite (disbarment action), 1987 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous
    - A-Bomb Testing 1952-1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Agent Orange - new law suit (Missouri) 2004-2005 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Air Force Life Today late 1980s (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Air Force Sexual Harassment Case, Pope AFB, NC 1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Amnesty for Anthrax (Deaton, Jeremy), 2001 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Anthrax - current, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Anthrax (vaccine), 1992-1998 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Artists for Amnesty, 1975 (Box Broadside 5064)
    - Erica Barker, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Jeff Bettendorf, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Sgt. Rose Black, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Citizen Soldier miscellany, 1971-1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Coast Guard, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Columbia - U. S. Military Involvement - "narco terrorists", 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Dependents (Schools, day care centers, health care, bowling alleys, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Depleted Uranium, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 14-15)
    - Fluoride/Aluminum, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Ft. Riley access (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Fielder, Cpl. Lance (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - ECCO file (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - "Citizen Soldier" newspapers, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Fundraising letters and flyers re: Safe Return and Amnesty for Vietnam Vets and Deserters, 1969-1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising letters and flyers re: Safe Return and Amnesty for Vietnam Vets and Deserters, 1976-1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - G.I. newspapers - Europe (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Getting Out Chapter - Discharges, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - GIPA News & Discussion Bulletin, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
    - Gustafson, Pfc. Nicholas, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Hawai'i, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Honduras, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Housing: on-base/off-base, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Iran Air/Vincennes Disaster, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Kelley, Lisa, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Leaving the Military (benefits, VA programs, etc., 1988 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Legal Challenges to the VA, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Living conditions (single GI's), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Litigation vs. weapons manufacturers, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Lundbom, Stephen, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Marines, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - McCook. Sgt. Larry, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Medical care (current crisis), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Military's Use against Drugs Issue, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - "Mortality Among Vietnam Veterans in Massachusetts 1972-1983" (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Flyers/News, 1985-1994 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - National Guard Coalition (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - NATO Bombing - Kosovo, Serbia, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - "On Guard" (G. I. newspaper)#1-15, 1986-1993 (Box 27, Folder 36-37)
    - Panama, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Peace & Freedom Campaign (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Persian Gulf/U.S.S. duty: Stark disaster (Navy), 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Petitions, Letters, etc. to Camilo Mejia (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Pool of Tears - Greg S. Raisden, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Re-enlistment, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Safe Return Amnesty (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
    - Toxic dump sites (military bases), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Transfer, change of station, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Tuition Aid: active duty Montgomery G. I. bill, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - U.S. Amnesty movement, 1972-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - U. S. and NATO (Europe), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Capt. Yousif Yee, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Submissions to publisher: A Life Worth Living, Carl Feingold memoirs, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Book proposal and distribution plan (final), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Chapter 1: Recruitment, reviews, 1989-1996 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Chapter 2: Basic Training, 1991-1995 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Chapter 3: Advanced Training, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Chapter 4: Life today (including benefits), 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Chapter 5: Military Justice, 1990-1994 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Chapter 6: Foreign Duty, 1990-1995 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Chapter 7: Minorities, 1989-1995 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Chapter 8: National Guard Reserves, 1987-1996 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Revisions: Military Life, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Fort Drum, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Fort Drum, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Cherry, Eugene, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Christa, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Gaskins, Brad A., 2007 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Publicity, Yolanda Huet-Vaughn, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, Yolanda Huet-Vaughn, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Khalil, Ghanim, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Mejia, Camillo, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Torres, Wilfredo, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Wade, Jacob, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Norfolk - PTSD Conf., 2010-2011 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - On Guard, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Publications (Box 28, Folder 15)
      -“The Khaki Closet”, “Real War Stories”, “Addicted to War”
    - "Veterans United Against the War" (VHS), 2002; V-7091 (Box 29)